<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Danceable</string>
    <string name="nav_list">List</string>
    <string name="nav_recording">Recognition</string>

    <!-- Dance Descriptions -->
    <string name="dance_cha_cha">
        Cha Cha / Cha Cha Cha
        A lively Latin partner dance with syncopated “cha‑cha‑cha” steps, playful hip motion, and rhythm that breaks on the 4th and 1st beats.
    </string>

    <string name="dance_discofox">
        Discofox
        A versatile social partner dance from the disco era, combining simple forward‑and‑back or side steps with turns and wraps; danced to 4/4 music and easy to pick up by beginners.
    </string>

    <string name="dance_jive">
        Jive
        A fast, energetic swing‑influenced dance with quick rock‑step and triple‑step (shuffle) footwork, often danced to upbeat music in social and competitive settings.
    </string>

    <string name="dance_quickstep">
        Quickstep
        A brisk, flowing ballroom dance evolved from foxtrot, featuring running steps, syncopations, and light hops; danced in a smooth style with continuous forward movement.
    </string>

    <string name="dance_rumba">
        Rumba
        A slow, sensual Latin ballroom dance emphasizing hip action and romantic connection, with smooth, deliberate steps and steady rhythm.
    </string>

    <string name="dance_salsa">
        Salsa
        A popular Latin partner dance with energetic footwork, rhythmically syncopated timing, spins, and dynamic lead‑follow patterns; danced in clubs worldwide.
    </string>

    <string name="dance_samba">
        Samba
        A rhythmic Latin dance from Brazil with a distinctive bounce action and forward‑backward steps, often seen in both social and competitive dance scenes.
    </string>

    <string name="dance_slow_waltz">
        Slow Waltz (English Waltz / Waltz)
        A graceful ballroom dance in 3/4 time with smooth, flowing rise‑and‑fall movements and elegant progress around the floor.
    </string>

    <string name="dance_tango">
        Tango
        A dramatic ballroom dance with sharp, staccato movements and purposeful pauses, expressing strong character and musical accents.
    </string>

    <string name="dance_viennese_waltz">
        Viennese Waltz
        A fast, rotating form of waltz in 3/4 time with continuous turns and sweeping movement around the floor; one of the oldest ballroom dances.
    </string>
    <string name="nav_detail">Detail</string>
</resources>